Guide to the New York City Central Labor Council Photographs Collection PHOTOS.020
Tamiment Library / Wagner Archives
- Series VI: PORTRAITS/INDIVIDUALS
  - QUINN, JAMES, undated (Box 10, Folder 254)
  - RANDOLPH, A. PHILIP PORTRAITS, undated (Box 10, Folder 255)
  - RANDOLPH, PHILIP – DAY, undated (Box 10, Folder 256)
  - RANDOLPH, PHILIP – WEEK, undated (Box 10, Folder 257)
  - RANDOLPH, PHILIP – 50th ANNIVERSARY SLEEPING CAR PORTERS, undated (Box 10, Folder 258)
  - ROBERTS, LILLIAN, undated (Box 10, Folder 259)
  - REUTHER, WALTER, undated (Box 10, Folder 260)
  - Portraits – Miscellaneous: Q+R, undated (Box 10, Folder 261)
  - SHANKER, ALBERT, undated (Box 10, Folder 262)
  - SOLZHENITSYN, A, undated (Box 10, Folder 263)
  - STOKOWSKI, LEOPOLD, undated (Box 10, Folder 264)
  - SULLIVAN, DAVE, undated (Box 10, Folder 265)
  - SWEENEY, JOHN, undated (Box 10, Folder 266)
  - Portraits – Miscellaneous: S, undated (Box 10, Folder 267)
  - TOOHY, ED, undated (Box 10, Folder 268)
  - VAN ARSDALE Jr., HARRY (VAN ARSDALE Folder # 1), undated (Box 10, Folder 269)
  - See also NP1 – Van Arsdale Jr., Harry, undated
  - VAN ARSDALE, HARRY (VAN ARSDALE Folder # 2), undated (Box 10, Folder 270)
  - VAN ARSDALE, HARRY (VAN ARSDALE Folder # 3), undated (Box 11, Folder 271)
  - VAN ARSDALE, THOMAS, undated (Box 11, Folder 272)
  - Portraits – Miscellaneous: T through V, undated (Box 11, Folder 273)
  - Portraits – Miscellaneous: W-Z, undated (Box 11, Folder 274)
  - PORTRAITS – MOUNTED – IDENTIFIED, undated (Box 11, Folder 275)
  - PORTRAITS – MOUNTED – UNIDENTIFIED, undated (Box 11, Folder 276)
  - PORTRAITS – unidentified, undated (Box 11, Folder 277)
- Series VII: PARADES
  - Subseries A. Easter
    - EASTER PARADE, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 278)
  - Subseries B. Labor Day
    - LABOR DAY PARADE – Year unknown, undated (Box 11, Folder 279)
    - LABOR DAY PARADE, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 280)
    - LABOR DAY PARADE, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 281)
    - LABOR DAY PARADE, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 282)
    - LABOR DAY PARADE – 1981 COMMITTEE MEETINGS (Box 12, Folder 283)
    - LABOR DAY PARADE – 1981 [1 of 2] (Box 12, Folder 284)
    - LABOR DAY PARADE – 1981 [2 of 2] (Box 12, Folder 285)
    - LABOR DAY PARADE – 1982 (Folder 1 of 2) (Box 12, Folder 286)
    - LABOR DAY PARADE – 1982 – (Folder 2 of 2) (Box 12, Folder 287)
    - LABOR DAY PARADE – 1983 Folder 1 of 3 (Box 12, Folder 288)
    - LABOR DAY PARADE – 1983 Folder 2 of 3 (Box 13, Folder 289)
    - LABOR DAY PARADE – 1983 Folder 3 of 3 (Box 13, Folder 290)
    - LABOR DAY PARADE, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 291)
    - LABOR DAY PARADE, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 292)
    - LABOR DAY PARADE, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 293)
    - LABOR DAY PARADE – (4x6 color snapshots), 1991 (Box 13, Folder 294)
    - LABOR DAY PARADE, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 295)
    - LABOR DAY PARADE, ca.1993 (Box 13, Folder 296)
    - LABOR DAY PARADE – 1995 (folder 1 of 2) (black and white; color) (Box 13, Folder 297)
    - LABOR DAY PARADE – 1995 – (folder 2 of 2) (b/w contact sheets; Miller photography) (Box 14, Folder 298)
    - LABOR DAY BREAKFAST and PARADE –(color contact sheets – Tom Matthews, photographer), 1996 (Box 14, Folder 299)
    - LABOR DAY PARADE, New York City. 84 4x6 color snapshots by photographer Al Eckman, “Hillsdale – 518-851-9807; NYC – 718-969-5615, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 300)
    - Subseries VII: C. May Day, undated
    - PARADE – MAY DAY, 1948 (Box 14, Folder 301)
  - Subseries D. St. Patrick’s Day
    - PARADE – ST. PATRICK, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 302)
    - ST. PATRICK’S DAY PARADE, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 303)
    - Subseries VII: E. Solidarity Day, undated
    - SOLIDARITY DAY, Jan 30, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 304)
    - SOLIDARITY DAY – PARADE MEETING, Aug 25, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 305)
- Series VIII: DEMONSTRATIONS
  - DEMOS UNIDENTIFIED, undated (Box 14, Folder 306)
  - DEMOS – ACTORS EQUITY – CONTRA UNESCO, Jan 1975 (Box 14, Folder 307)
  - DEMOS ACWU – Against Clothing Imports, undated (Box 14, Folder 308)
  - DEMOS – ACWU – FARAH, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 309)
  - DEMOS – ACWU – FARAH, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 310)
  - DEMOS – ACWU – JP STEVENS, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 311)
  - DEMOS – ACWU – JP STEVENS, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 312)
  - DEMOS – ACWU – JP STEVENS, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 313)
  - DEMOS – ACTWU – OSHA, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 314)
  - DEMOS AFSCME – LINCOLN HOSPITAL, undated (Box 14, Folder 315)
  - DEMOS – AFT – NEWARK TEACHERS UNION, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 316)
  - DEMOS – AFT – CHRIST THE KING, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 317)
  - DEMOS – AFTRA – WINS, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 318)
  - DEMOS AGMA – STRIKE AGAINST NY PHILHARMONIC, undated (Box 15, Folder 319)
  - DEMOS – APWU, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 320)
  - DEMOS – ATU – BUS DRIVERS, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 321)
  - DEMOS – ATU – GREYHOUND, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 322)
  - DEMOS BAKERY AND CONFECTIONARY WORKERS, undated (Box 15, Folder 323)
  - DEMOS – BUILDINGS + CONSTRUCTION TRADE COUNCIL, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 324)
  - DEMOS – CIVIL RIGHTS RALLIES – various dates, undated (Box 15, Folder 325)
  - DEMOS – CWA, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 326)
  - DEMOS – CWA – AT&T, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 327)
  - DEMOS DEPARTMENT STORE AND RETAIL WORKERS, undated (Box 15, Folder 328)
  - DEMOS ENGINEERING AND PROFESSIONAL GUILD – LOCAL 66, undated (Box 15, Folder 329)
  - DEMOS – HOSPITAL WORKERS, undated (Box 15, Folder 330)
  - DEMOS – HOTEL AND RESTAURANT WORKERS, undated (Box 15, Folder 331)
  - DEMOS – IAM – COLT MENASCO, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 332)
  - DEMOS – IATSE – ABC, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 333)
  - DEMOS IBEW – LOCAL 3, undated (Box 15, Folder 334)
  - DEMOS – IBEW – CBS, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 335)
  - DEMOS I.U.E – Local 463, undated (Box 15, Folder 336)
  - DEMOS – I.U.E – ANACONDA, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 337)
  - DEMOS – I.U.E – GE, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 338)
  - DEMOS – LABORERS’ INT. UNION – Local 1207, undated (Box 15, Folder 339)
  - DEMOS – Lillian Roberts (Free Lillian Roberts), 1968 (Box 15, Folder 340)
  - DEMOS – MEDICARE, undated (Box 15, Folder 341)
  - DEMOS – MONDALE RALLY, undated (Box 15, Folder 342)
  - DEMOS NABET – ABC (DISNEY), undated (Box 15, Folder 343)
  - DEMOS NABET – National Black Network Strike, undated (Box 15, Folder 344)
  - DEMOS – NABET – NBC, undated (Box 15, Folder 345)
  - DEMOS – NALC, Feb 1979 (Box 15, Folder 346)
  - DEMOS – NATHANS, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 347)
  - DEMOS – NEW YORKERS UNITED DAY, undated (Box 15, Folder 348)
  - DEMOS – N.Y. HOTEL + MOTEL TRADES COUNCIL, undated (Box 16, Folder 349)
  - DEMOS – NEWSPAPER GUILD, NEW YORK – STRIKE, ca.1966 (Box 16, Folder 350)
  - DEMOS – NEWSPAPER GUILD – NY POST, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 351)
  - DEMOS – OPEIU – GHI, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 352)
  - DEMOS – PATCO, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 353)
  - DEMOS – PARAMUTUAL CLERKS – AQUEDUCT, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 354)
  - DEMOS – POLICE AND FIREFIGHTERS, undated (Box 16, Folder 355)
  - DEMOS – PRICES, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 356)
  - DEMOS – PROFESSIONAL STAFF CONGRESS, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 357)
  - DEMOS – R.W.D.S.U – MACY’S, A+S, LORD + TAYLOR, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 358)
  - DEMOS – RWDSU District 65 – BLOOMINGDALES, undated (Box 16, Folder 359)
  - DEMOS – SAG/AFTRA, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 360)
  - DEMOS – SEIU – CARSON PARK HOSPITAL, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 361)
  - DEMOS – SEIU – PICKET, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 362)
  - DEMOS – SHANKER, A. – JAILING, undated (Box 16, Folder 363)
  - DEMOS – SHOE WORKERS, undated (Box 16, Folder 364)
  - DEMOS – SOCIAL SECURITY RALLY, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 365)
  - DEMOS – SOVIET JEWRY, undated (Box 16, Folder 366)
  - DEMOS – TAXI DRIVERS, undated (Box 16, Folder 367)
  - DEMOS – TAXI DRIVERS – MADISON SQUARE RALLY, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 368)
  - DEMOS – TEACHERS, PROFESSORS, AND SUPPORT STAFF, undated (Box 16, Folder 369)
  - DEMOS – TEXTILE WORKERS, undated (Box 16, Folder 370)
  - DEMOS – TWU – FLIGHT ATTENDANTS, undated (Box 16, Folder 371)
  - DEMOS – TWU – TRANSIT RALLY, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 372)
    - DEMOS – TWU – CONTINENTAL – 1984, and PATCO, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 375)
  - DEMOS –TWU – ARGENTINE AIRLINES, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 373)
  - DEMOS – TWU – EASTERN AIRLINES, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 374)
  - DEMOS – (NY) TYPOGRAPHICAL UNION No. 6, undated (Box 16, Folder 376)
  - DEMOS – UFW – HUNTER COLLEGE RALLY, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 377)
  - DEMOS – UFW – BOYCOTT, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 378)
  - DEMOS – UFWA – LA-Z-BOY CHAIR, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 379)
- Series IX: ELECTORAL POLITICS
  - Subseries A. Voters Registration
    - REGISTRATION DRIVE, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 380)
    - REGISTRATION DRIVE, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 381)
    - REGISTRATION DRIVE, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 382)
  - Subseries B. Election Campaigns
    - CAMPAIGN – UNITED LABOR COMMITTEE, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 383)
    - CAMPAIGN – STEVENSON, Oct 10, 1956 (Box 17, Folder 384)
    - CAMPAIGN – HARRISON for NEW YORK STATE GOVERNOR, 1956 (Box 17, Folder 385)
    - CAMPAIGN – WAGNER PRIMARY, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 386)
    - ELECTIONS, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 387)
    - CAMPAIGN – CARTER TRAIN – PENN STA., Sep 20, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 388)
    - ELECTIONS, Nov 5, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 389)
    - CARTER, PRES. J. – CITY HALL, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 390)
    - ELECTIONS – October 1978 (New York Gubernatorial) (Box 17, Folder 391)
- Series X: OTHER ORGANIZATIONS
  - Convention – Brotherhood of Sleeping Car Porters, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 392)
  - INSTALLATION – May 1972 (Local 1199), undated (Box 17, Folder 393)
  - National Committee for Labor Israel, undated (Box 17, Folder 394)
  - UNION LABEL + SERVICE TRADES, undated (Box 17, Folder 395)
  - CAVALCADE OF SKILLS – UNION LABEL + SERVICE TRADES, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 396)
  - UNITED FARM WORKERS, undated (Box 17, Folder 397)
  - UNITED FARM WORKERS – CESAR CHAVEZ RECEPTION, Dec 19, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 398)
  - UNITED FARM WORKERS DAY, May 10, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 399)
  - UNITED FARM WORKERS – CITY HALL, Jun 25, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 400)
- Series XI: Copy Negatives
  - (5x7 copy neg.) LABOR DAY PARADE—Grand Marshall Lane shakes hands w/ Cardinal in front of St. Patrick’s Cathedral, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 401)
  - (5x7 copy neg.) LABOR DAY PARADE—NYS Gubernational Candidate Mario Cuomo and his wife Matilda, on reviewing stand, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 402)
  - (5x7 copy neg.) LABOR DAY PARADE—New York Gubernational Candidate, Mario Cuomo, and his wife, marching in Parade, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 403)
  - (5x7 copy neg.) LABOR DAY PARADE—(1) Grand Marshall Sandy Feldman and others march; (2) Lane Kirkland(?) addresses crowd, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 404)
  - (8x10 copy neg.) Portraits-B (Bahr, Morton), undated (Box 17, Folder 405)
  - (8x10 copy neg.) Portraits-O (O’Brien, Peter), undated (Box 17, Folder 406)
  - (8x10 copy neg) Randolph, A. Philip, undated (Box 17, Folder 407)
  - (8x10 neg.) Portraits—Shanker, Albert, undated (Box 17, Folder 408)
  - (8x10 copy neg.) Portraits—Sweeney, John, undated (Box 17, Folder 409)
  - (8x10 copy negs.) Misc. Unidentified, undated (Box 17, Folder 410)
- Series XII: Oversized Prints
- Series XIII: Unprocessed